It has begun!
Channel
Congratulations!
It's started!
A memorable one.
May I begin?
The first commemorative
The first commemorative transmission is brought to you by us.
Good evening.
You know, we have something in common.
Have you noticed?
Do you know?
Since some of you are new here, I'd like to introduce myself one by one.
Okay, first of all, Mii-san.
Yes, Mi-chan.
Mi-chan.
Hello.
Good morning. My name is Minami Koike.
I'm from Hyogo.
Born in Hyogo Prefecture.
Miichan from Hyogo.
Then, I am.
Yes, I am.
Good evening. I'm Hina Inoue.
Wow.
How do you do it?
I'm from Hyogo, too.
Please.
Hyogo girl.
Then, Yui, please continue. Go ahead.
Yes, I'm Yui Takemoto from Shiga Prefecture.
I'm Yui Takemoto from Shiga Prefecture, a powerful girl born of beautiful white hair.
Please do.
Then, let's continue,
Hono.
Tamura.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Tamura Hono of Sakurazaka 46.
I'm from Osaka.
Osaka.
That's great.
Next, Karin.
Karin.
Hello.
Good evening.
I'm Fujiyoshi Karin from Sakurazaka 46.
I'm from Osaka.
Really?
Something like that.
I'm from Osaka. Please.
Please do.
Next, Kira-chan.
Bird, bird.
What was that?
A powerful girl from Hyogo.
Cute.
Born in Hyogo Prefecture.
Yes, I'm Kira Masumoto, 21 years old.
I'm Kira Masumoto, 21 years old.
This is difficult. I don't know how you guys have it.
It's like that.
Like that?
I was born in Hyogo Prefecture.
Then, did everyone introduce themselves?
Yes, we did.
Common points.
We are members of the Kansai region.
We are from Kansai.
So we are all members of the Kansai region,
I can already see it,
I can see it.
I'm going to do a live delivery while enjoying okonomiyaki and takoyaki,
I would like to do live delivery in a relaxed manner.
Please do so.
There are too many cameras.
It's amazing.
Now that's great.
This is great.
This one, too.
Which one?
Which one?Which one?
Is this one here, too?
What's that?
Not at all.
Which one? This one?
This one?
That's not how we play.
Sorry, I made a mistake.
Okay, everybody, let's get back to work.
Oh, my God.
It's been too long.
I'm sorry.
Can we get on with it now?
We're hungry, right?
Yes, I am.
Okonomiyaki.
Something like that,
I just got an iPad,
I've been reading all the comments here,
I'm looking at them.
Hey, everyone.
What are you calling me, Ren-chan?
What?
You don't have anything like that?
You don't think so?
Everyone says you have a face that can withstand a close-up.
Over there.
Let's take this with us.
Thank you very much.
I'll call on you often.
Please do.
Yes, I'll call on you often.
Want some?
I'm hungry.
What do you want to do?
Welcome home.
You've never cooked before?
No way.
I've never made it myself.
What?
Why not?
Do you know how to make it?
Why do you say Kansai if you don't know how to make it?
That's crazy.
There are takoyaki.
You don't have takoyaki?
I used to make them all the time,
But maybe not as much as takoyaki.
On weekends and Golden Week, it's okonomiyaki.
We would cook okonomiyaki on weekends and during Golden Week.
So, do you divide into two teams, the okonomiyaki team and the takoyaki team?
Yes.
Do you want takoyaki?
I want takoyaki.
That's right.
Takoyaki then.
I want okonomiyaki, too.
Which one do you want?
Then, I'll have takoyaki, too.
Let's change the red one once.
Which one is takoyaki?
This one is takoyaki.
Takoyaki are classmates.
That's right.
Really?
2000.
2001?
2002?
You were born early.
We're classmates, aren't we?
Well, let's go get the ingredients.
Sorry about the back.
Can you see this?
Yes, it's on.
Look at this.
You want to take it with you on camera?
Everybody calm down.
Right hand.
That's okay.That's okay.
What do you want me to do?
We're still cousins.
Come on, make takoyaki with your cousin.
Okay.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
Desk feet.
You want to do this? Cut the takoyaki.
This is okonomiyaki.
Is it natural?
What should we put in the okonomiyaki?
What should I put in it?
I have a recommendation.
Cabbage and pork.
Do you know this?
What's this?
Beef sinew and konnyaku.
You put beef sinew in it?
Thank you.
Anko bean paste.
Okonomiyaki with red bean paste?
There is this, isn't there?
Like takoyaki monja.
The sweet kind.
I didn't know that.
Like monja.
What's it called?
It's like anko maki.
Anko rolls?
Why are you so skeptical?
Is that Kansai food?
Kebabs?
What do you want?
Somebody's life.
Shall we toast?
I'll drink to that when we eat.
No?
Let's have one more toast later.
What's the point?
Hey!
Nothing.
Let's put it in this.
Not cabbage.
No problem.
Thank you.
Here's another one.
You'll put this in, right?
Why did you say that?
I don't dance.
You don't dance?
Misato-san said she was making okonomiyaki.
You said you were going to put noodles in.
No, I didn't.
Good luck with Misato-san.
Yakisoba.
Can I have yakisoba?
Misato-san's hands.
Takemoto-san's face.
Shall we add cabbage?
Let's put cabbage.
You should push it.
They'll eat it together.
Calm down.
This is okonomiyaki.
This way is takoyaki.
Then...
We have to mix them.
Do you want cabbage, Hono-chan?
TakoyakiTakoyaki.
I'll mix it from the bottom.
Let's mix it once.
But still...
It could be a little more.
Thank you very much.
Please wait a moment.
I'm working hard right now.
I'm working hard on it.I'm making it.
I am
We are
Okonomiyaki.
If it's a small one
Do you want to put a little more in?
Okonomiyaki.
Which one is it?
Do you want a different kind?
Thank you very much.
This one is better.
Like this.
Oil.
Oil?
Give the big one to the okonomiyaki team.
I'll mix it.
Is there a trawler in there?
That's a lot of oil.
Oil?
Is that rolled up kitchen paper?
What do you recommend?
Put them in, in order.
The recommended contents.
It's warm.
It's a mess.
You're putting tissues in there?
Of course.
I'll just use kitchen paper.
I'll put some more in.
Let it soak in.
No, thank you.
I guess it depends on the person.
I'll go get some.
It's delicious if you put it in.
I'll put some more in.
Thank you very much.
You want some of this, too?
What's that sound like?
I'll put it in.
That's OK.
Do you want to put some more in?
Is that enough?
Is okonomiyaki different from okonomiyaki?
Okonomiyaki is...
It's okonomiyaki.
I said put more in.
Can you see the okonomiyaki?
You can see it?
It's more sludgy.
This is it,
Can you fit this in?
It should go in more.
Do you want to try one more time?
Shall I put some more in?
The okonomiyaki team is struggling.
They're struggling, struggling, struggling.
Second time vs.
It's like one against two.
Look at this.
They're putting too much in.
This is good.
Really?
Is it hard to hear you guys?
What is our team doing?
I don't know...
Kira, oil.
I thought you were going to let us in.
No, I didn't.
I mixed the oil, didn't I?
Kitchen paper.
I forgot.
Not kitchen paper.
It's fine.
Put some oil on it.
It'll work.
I think we can make a big one.
I can't put 10 or something in it.
It's hot when I say 10.
I can't.I am.
Can we go without for once?
It's a recommendation.
I won't put it in.
I'll put it on later.
I don't want green onions.
Green onions?
Do you want to borrow a makeup brush from the makeup artist?
But it's okay, it's okay.
I'll be fine in the end.
It's totally fine.
Can I mix them?
Yes, you can.
Shall we go that way?
Just a little bit.
I'm going to put this in.
Okay, I'll put it in.
I'll put in the dough for the takoyaki team.
Pick one.
Choose?
Do you have chocolate?
That's right.
There is a lot of it.
If you put the dregs together
It tends to go bad.
What is this? Mentaiko?
I'm making it.
Hey, look, everyone.
Why are they showing us?
Because I'm here.
I'm sorry, this is hard.
I'm really worried about your team.
Did you put oil on the floor?
I did.
We had to stretch the oil.
I didn't stretch it.
We had to stretch it.
There was no chechin paper to stretch it.
It's kind of sludgy, isn't it?
But is it?
What kind of okonomiyaki do you make at home?
Is it different from ours?
Is the okonomiyaki team only using cabbage so far?
No, they don't.
Tell him.
It's the Inukami Special.
My hometown is...
That's my hometown.
It's called "korotama.
It's filled with konnyaku and beef tendon.
Looks delicious, doesn't it?
Okonomiyaki.
Isn't there a little okonomiyaki sauce?
Octopus hardens.
What about that?
What about that one?
Is it okay now?
What about the cabbage?
I want you to take the oil out.
Isn't that too little okonomiyaki?
Really?
Is this enough for one slice?
It should be enough to overflow.
Takoyaki.
Here you go.
Cut the takoyaki.
Go ahead.
It's cute.
Did you do that?
Sorry if you don't like the sound.
I'm going to grill it now.
I'm going to burn it.
I'm sorry. You don't like the sound.
It looks good.
You see, that's what this is. Takoyaki is a kind of takoyaki
is to put a lot of dough.
It's to make it overflow.
Wait a minute.
It's not dirty.
It's not what it looks like now.Not now.
Don't project it.
It's not that it's dirty, right?
That's right. It's not that it's dirty.
It's just that when you put a lot of takoyaki in, it becomes round.
Takoyaki.
That's why they intentionally overflowed.
You can't see the takoyaki.
I'm making it into okonomiyaki.
It's spread out a little bit.
So this is how you put it together.
Tako, how far did you put in the takoyaki?
But I'm sorry.
It's not Inoe's special anymore. I'm sorry.
I put in the octopus.
There was an incident.
It wasn't lit.
So it's okay.
It's okay.
It happens.
It's gorgeous.
You're going to do it, aren't you?
It's a little too much dough.
It's a lot of fabric, I'm sure.
John, it's okay... but a little bit is possible... because the sun wasn't shining...
I'm not saying that because it didn't get any sun.
I'm sure you'll put in cabbage, but not cabbage...
Who's just bad-mouthing the director?
Bum!
I'll put this on...
I'll put in some green onions and two slices of leeks.
I'll put in two slices of green onion.
I'm sure you'll see what I'm talking about.
I'm just pointing out that we've already done this once with Stuke.
I see... we always do half octopus, half winter, and I always put in the chocolate.
I've been told my okonomiyaki is too small, so I eat a lot of it.
I'll do a lot of different things... like turn it over once... and if it cooks a certain way... that's all right, right?
I can write about it, but not a little bit
I can write about it, but I have to turn it over, even a little bit, or it'll be too late.
Boober money!
walking I can run but would you recommend 24?
nadamily what happens to carcinogenesis box at the same time thank you
I can go, I can go, I can go, I can go, I can go, I can go, I can go, I can go!
I'm sure I'm holding on to my toe, but I'm not sure if I'm holding on to my toe.
But a jammed toe is a big deal... but it's just a cashier and a little girl, you know...
It's a pain... but it's a little too much... and it hurts... so I'm going to have to stop you... from stretching out your cab.
I've got a little bit of a problem... but I've got a little bit of a problem... and I've got a little bit of a problem... and I've got a little bit of a problem...
I'm going to turn it over, please...
I'm going to turn it over...
I'm sorry.
goo, it's great, it's great!
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Yeah, so give me a score that I can make another one.
I know it's not the same, but it's got a nice feel to it, that's what it's all about.
Thank you for the bag, I'm thinking of someone making something, someone making okonomiyaki with me
I think they're eating it together
Boober cat
nam No, I don't.
I'm making it again, Akira-chan!
I'm making it again, Saakira-chan!
I'm not sure if it's this way, but I'm sure it's this way because I don't want to have to eat this.
I don't have any air.
I don't have any more oil, oil that you don't have, what should I do with it?
I'm sure it hasn't hardened, or at least not on the surface like this But it won't happen the first time, not even once
It's like that before, so I'm going to cut it high and see if the really high sun comes through, it'll be nice.
I'm sorry, I'm over here right now, so if you'd raised the delivery catcher properly, you wouldn't have been able to get it.
ah ha ha, you don't turn it upside down - this one's going to go this way, eh?
I'll plan and put it in, but now it's just a bunch of crap I'll just say it's a bunch of crap
Yes, Durham.
I'll shut up about Mr. More and 13.
I think we could have made the dough a lot more... a lot more...
I'm going to call you "takoyaki".
My cheeks are glutinous like takoyaki!
I've been to the caterer six times, so today was a gala.
I've been eating it my whole life.
I don't know. I put rice cakes and cheese.
The makeup artist said, "Oh, no!
So this is it.
How's it going? How are Mi-chan and Inoue?How's it going? How are Mi-chan and Inoue?
Mi-chan's working on an original. Is this your first time?
Oh! Absolutely delicious!
Do you think it's good with cheese?
Like kimcheeze?
Kimcheese is the best? Isn't kimcheeze good with okonomiyaki too?
Mentaiko
Hungry?
Thank you.
You want to keep it all?
I guess so.
I'm a mother who wears it like a sky.
P-k-mio, boobar, yes, that's right.
Paso, I'm bathing you, kid. I'll tell you what.
I'll probably say it.
I'll probably say "bathing.
I tried my best. It's a squeeze, but there's a lot more in there.
I'm sorry, I don't know.
I'm sorry, I don't know... and I'm sure you're going to hear it, and you're going to tell me to stay put... because some of you might have already finished dinner.
If you put them all in, it'll be the first time you've ever done that.
Don't go over there with this bach, you guys... do it to Oriko... and maybe I'll let you do it to me, too.
What?
Mochi and cheese is so good! Thanks for your funny comments.
Thanks for all the interesting comments.
I think it's the right thing to do, no mistakes, don't talk so loud.
I'm sure there's no mistake... and there's no difference... but the writing is a little burned out.
I made it more than that... and I've made it before... and we'll eat it together.
It's a little difficult to get it right.
I'm just going to shape it like this, and then I'll give it a solo edge.
I'd like to get the color right and the shape just a little bit more... six flowers, six people... yes... maybe I should have gone a little lower...
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a good deal on a new dress
Thanks for going to eat McGee!
I'm going to go eat some of that... but I think I'd better share it with you... so we can share it together.
Tiga, you're so cheerful.
I'm sure you'll be happy to know that I know what you're talking about.
I'm not sure if it's too late to do it now, but if I do it now, it'll be too late, and it'll burn a little.
No, it's absolutely fine. It could have flown.
I'm sure it's fine, but I might have flown in with an IPO of a few things.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to cut it once I'm done with it, but I'm going to try it and see if it works.
Political District .... This is a great izogram!
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get the job done.
I'm not going to cut the pork, thank you very much, please cut the pork.
Ahoy!
I've said it, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
I'll make a toast.
I'm surprised, I'm surprised, I'm surprised.
I don't usually drink soda.
Mii... Oh, that's right, Mii. I'm Mii. Thank you very much.
You won't make okonomiyaki this time, right?
I'll make okonomiyaki this time too.
I guess so. But I'd like to make something unexpected next time.
Oh, really?
Oh, but I said "amphire".
Wait a minute.
Oh, are you sure?
But I'll totally accept it.
Yes, I'll take it. Thank you very much.
Producer's meal.
This is ready.
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, it fell out.
I don't know about this.
Who's going to be the first to eat it? Let's see.
This?
Oh, yes.
Well, first things first,
Let's put it on this.
Time for the wakumi-yaki.
Is it ready?
It's ready.
Mr. Inoue, we have orange juice.
What kind of orange juice is this, Mr. Inoue?
I can tell.
I can tell by its appearance.
Does it look good?
Shall I put it on this?
It's still a little bit ready.
How about this? Does it look good?
Yeah, but..,
Is it good? This one.Is it good? This.
I didn't put any meat in it.
That's right.
You're pouring something.
He's pouring something for me.
Ginger ale for Inoue.
Oh, did you pour it in?
Yes, I did.
But Kira-chan has orange juice.
Shall we drink this one time?
Oh, oh, oh,
What does that mean?
Do you want me to drink two?
I'll have two glasses, Inoue.
I'll have two.
I'll have two drinks.
I have an hour and a half.
I've been dancing today.
It's already been about an hour.
Here you go, Ami.
Okay, bye.
The real one,
Urunchan.
Let's sit down once.
I'll take this one.
This is where you were before.
This?
The real one, then.
Thank you.
Don't go back where you were.
I'll take a glass, too.
What's this?
Mine too.
Sorry, Ken-chan.
Thank you.
What should I do? What should I do?
Oh, what is it?
Thank you, thank you.
It's amazing.
Isn't it amazing?
This look.
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
Are you okay?
Oh, oh, oh, oh. Accident.
Where should I put this?
What's that noise?
It's like Christmas.
There's a gap in the med bottle.
Can we cut it?
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
Jingle, jingle, jingle, jingle.
No one will help me. I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Can I close it again? Okay. It's really hard.
The cap is hard to open.
I'm telling you.
I'm not sure if this one's right or not.
Is that wrong? One time.
Cheers. Do you want a pie? Not when you eat all of it?
It's ready.
Sauce, just now.
You want to do it all?
I'm out.
Thank you.
Can I put this in, too? Boom, boom, boom.
Yes, I do. You coming back?
Give me a plate.
I'll pass the plate around.
Everybody give me a plate.
Well, well, well.
I'll probably overlook this.
I'm not sure I can overlook this... but that's exactly what I'm going to do.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to have a white bridge, but I'm sure it's a good idea to have a white bridge, too.
I'm sure you'll be able to find someone who can help you.
I'm sure there's something to the name of the guy in front of Carnève, or the guy in front of the horse.
voor please accept this government office cabaret very familiar
I'm sure you're familiar with this government office cabaret!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Well, I'm not going to go to the school
Point and dry ah!
boo boo dream
I'm only good in the shadows when I'm in a fight and the board fee is good, and you're not pronouncing me right!
Wooly's a dickhead and a raw mass.
I didn't get to know Karin very well.
I didn't get to know Ekarin well.
I'm sorry, I've been waiting for you.
It's already been 30 minutes... and only one more to go.
I've only got one more to go.
I'm going to drink the chica at the booth... and I didn't even bother to arm myself with mayonnaise...
I'm not going to tell you what to do with the arm, but I'm going to go to a lot of trouble with the mayonnaise.
Hey, let's lay out some humanity!
Hey, but it's a big assortment. It's getting prettier.
It's pretty now? It's still the same.
Bon appétit, everyone!
It's done!
One time.
One more time.
I'm putting mayonnaise on it now.
I'm putting mayonnaise on it.
I'm putting mayonnaise on now.
I put something on it.
Oh, my sleeves!
My sleeves!
My sleeves! My sleeves!
The length is about to hang up.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Right away, right away
Right away, sir!
Come here.
Yes, yes.
Hey...
Let's have a toast.
Hey, suddenly...
We each have a juice.
What did you drink?
What would you like to drink?
Ginger ale.
Ginger ale for me too.
And then?
Coke.
Water.
Water for me too.
Miron-chan.
Inoue's orange juice.
Everyone loves Gari-chan, and they put a lot of it in my drink.
They drank two glasses of it.
What do you mean?
I poured it on my own.
I thought he'd drink my juice.
I'll have some.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
So let's have a toast.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers.
Wait a minute.
Can I ask you a favor, Yuka-chan?
Me?
It's a memorable first time.
Today is a memorable live delivery.
Congratulations.
Let's work hard to increase the number of subscribers to our channel even more,
And let's do our best to make many, many more interesting live broadcasts.
Cheers everyone!
Cheers!
It's delicious. Let's have it.
First, Inoue made okonomiyaki.
What did you put in it? Konnyaku and beef tendon.
Konnyaku and beef tendon.
Sweet and spicy. It's called "korotama".
Korotama. Hyogo?Korotama. Hyogo?
Yes, maybe. You want some? We'll eat it first.
It's called korotama? Korotama.
Let's try it and eat it.
Wait, Karin's just now.
I'm putting that in there. Don't you want to put it on top?
Which one? You want this one? This one.
Oh, yeah.
That might be it. Thank you.
It's sharp.
There it is! There it is! There's konjac!
Is everyone all right? I hope I'm not missing anything, konjac
Konnyaku!
Four days, wait
I asked for the temperature, but they said "mmm
Please wait!
Takane, I've been on the boat for 4 weeks, and I fainted
No, no, no, please adjust the temperature, I'll take it, I'll take it, I'll take it
Well, first of all, I'm a dog...
It's made with konnyaku and beef tendon simmered in a sweet and spicy sauce, and it's called korodama.
It's called "korodama", but I guess you know it for the first time.
I don't know anything about it.
Maybe he lives there.
Is it good?
The batter is fluffy, like a pancake.
The batter is fluffy like a pancake, it's delicious, like a pastry, and it leaves a thick, sweet residue, it's definitely good, I haven't had it in a long time.
I haven't had food like this in a long time.
I wish I could have found it sooner. It's so good. It's good? It's so good! It's so good!
Is there pork on it?
Yes, yes, I put it on. It's baked well. This way today?
Yeah, it's so good today.
I've never had it before.
Here it is.
Delicious.
But... speaking of Kansai, there's that guy.
The youngest Tenshukan.
You're the youngest, Ten-Can.
Why isn't he here today?
He's young today.
He's still in high school.
He's young.
Mmm.
Delicious.
You see it?
Heavenly.
Mnh-mnh.
Tenchan.
I wonder if she's awake. She said she's fine to watch.
I'll check, everyone.
Not that many people.
There you go.
Do you want to hear her voice?
Do you want to hear her voice? Was that on the tablet?
Do you want to hear it?
If I call you, will you call me?
I would.
You would?
Let's call him.
Is that okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, you're gonna do it?
How's it going? What are they saying?
They want to hear about it?
Did you do it? Yes, yes, yes.
Did you spill it?
No, I didn't.
I didn't spill it.
Did you spill it?
He wants to hear it. He wants to hear it.
He wants to hear it. - He wants to hear it. I made some calls.
Dad, you're on the 100,000 person list.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
There's so many.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Can you guys hear me?
What's going on?What's going on?
What's going on?
What's wrong? Heavenly Father.
What's going on over here?
Hey there, Ten-chan.
Good work.
What were you doing?
Watching.
You were watching?
Yeah. I was watching while I was drying my hair.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ten-chan.
It takes time to dry your hair, doesn't it?
It's so long.
I'm listening to a long story.
I'm glad I didn't spread it out.
I was going to.
What are you doing now?
I'm making okonomiyaki and takoyaki.
They all have their own specialties.
Ten-chan recommends what to put in them.
Takoyaki or okonomiyaki, do you have any suggestions?
Eh?
Can you hear me?
Not much.
Not much?
I don't like takoyaki.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Takoyaki? Takoyaki? Ten-san.
Takoyaki? I like takoyaki.
Oh, really?
You have takoyaki too?
What? Not takoyaki? Just regular octopus.
I already put it in.
Not octopus?
Thank you very much. You've done us a great service.
Yes, it is, but not octopus?
Ready?
What? What phone call? What's this phone for?
Oh, hey, Ten-chan. We're almost there.
Just 30 more people to go.
They say 100,000 people.
Oh, really.
They confirmed it.
It's true. That's right. They confirmed it.
If you have any message for the people who are watching now, please let me know.
I've been watching the chat.
Any messages?
A message? Well, there was a comment about, uh, something about, uh, beautiful whites of your eyes.
White eyes who? Who? Is it me?
Who is it?
I don't know who it was, but someone said I had beautiful whites of the eyes.
Who was it? Is that what you thought?
Did you sign up, Mr. Heaven?
Oh, you're registered. I am.
Oh, I really know.
Really?
Yeah, I did.
Let's get together and have a lot of fun.
I guess so.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Especially.
Lale, that was cool.
Oh, really?
You looked great.
Thank you.
Get lots of rest.
Don't take a break.
Thank you. Sorry.
Bye-bye.
You're getting up?
Can you stay up? Can you talk to me?
Have I ever triggered it?
Sure.
I'll see if I can get you all to say something.
Again?Again?
Did I give it to you?
One more time.
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button.
Please do.
You should say something, Mr. Fujii.
Sure thing.
Tenchan.
What is it?
I'll be in touch.
OK.
Anytime. Whenever you're ready.
Anytime?
I don't dare press the hang up button, so I'll just leave it here.
Oh, well.
Okay, bye-bye.
You're so sweet.
Thank you. Bye, Tenchan.
Good night.
Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
Bye bye.
Bye-bye.
See you tomorrow.
Bye bye.
I'm sorry.
I have to go. Mr. Burrell, everyone.
I'm cut off.
He hung up.
Did you cut it off, Mr. Ten?
Yes, I'll make it again, but I'm making it now, but I haven't really made it yet.
I'm sure you can get takoyaki, takoyaki, takoyaki, takoyaki.
What kind of place are you going to?
I'm sure you can get takoyaki, too!
It's sticky and delicious, and it's pretty hard to find.
Mochi and cheese or Mentai chocolate?
I'm curious about chocolate, but do you put it in takoyaki or okonomiyaki?
I'm not sure if it's a sweet version of takoyaki or a sweet version of takoyaki, but it's a good idea.
What's missing, boo boo boo!
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do it.
Pro, pro, pro, pro!
I wonder if it's the case of Mr. Soul...
Okay, Ami-chan, you want to say a few words?
Let's change inside.
Mi-chan, this is...
What do you want to do on youtube in the future?
Please make it a project, Mr. Pom and I'll meet for the first time
That's amazing!
No, it's more like two flash maniacs dressed as Pom, going to see him one more time, to see how he'll react
I'm not sure if that's a good idea, but I want to congratulate him.
I want to congratulate you. Please do it.
I'd like to congratulate Pom and Yui on their first meeting.
I'm sorry, thank you.
I'd like to do it because Fujikichi and I were looking for people to answer questions.
I'll answer your questions. I'm just trying to make it.
I was trying to answer your question, I was trying to answer your question, I was trying to answer your question, I was trying to answer your question, I was trying to answer your question, I was trying to answer your question, I was trying to answer your question, I was trying to answer your question, I was trying to answer your question!
I don't have cabbage, so I asked you a question...
thank you very much, you can write about me tomorrow
Thanks, this is takoyaki sauce.
I put bean paste in it... wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Then, in this miyakia... everyone sent in questions.
Where's the order? What kind of chocolate should I put in it?
This is nice. Andis's.
I'm sorry, I'm going to have to lean over and eat it...
Funo's making okonomiyaki.
A little bit of chocolate might be a little too sweet
We don't have much to do now that everyone's reading.
I'm making takoyaki, and when I saw Karin, I gave her some okonomiyaki sauce.
Rin-chan got depressed and brought it in.
Chocolate and red bean paste... and questions for everyone!
This is great! We put rice cakes in it!
But it's a little bit of everything! I don't know how it's going to turn out, but it's going to be sweet!
I don't think it'll be enough, but if we put some more bean jam in it, it'll make a good bed.
I'll lie down with you later...
A little more...
Challenger... one more question... if you had a family of 6, who would be the family members?
The common one. The common one.
Is there a mother-like member, or if there are six of you, who would be the father and who would be the mother?Is there any mother-like member or who is the father and who is the mother of these six members?
Idiots? Yes.
Let's start with the father, shall we?
Let's try Dad, let's try Dad, let's try Dad, Dad, Dad...
Okay, I've decided... Dad, okay, everyone's okay...
Kali! Kali!
Kari, Takemoto, look...
Karin has 3 votes.
Oh, Fujiwestern's here too. Didn't you see him? No, no, no, no, he was looking at me.
He was looking at me so hard, he said Fujiwestern was there too.
That means Karin got four votes. Karin, your father.
Who's Karin, Inoue?
Inoue? What are you really thinking?
That's right... your hearts are in the right place.
Anrahiko? Ah...
Is that right? But he's like the pillar of the family.
Like he's the pillar of the family. Like he's your father, quietly watching over you.
Who said daddy, Motome-chan? Inoue.
Why? Why?
He's so solid. When I went to Motone's house, her room was so clean.
I wonder what he'll say. I wonder what he'll say.
He's so neat, but he's also funny.
Is that what dads are like? If he was like that, he'd be funny.
That makes me happy.
And Inoue? Why? Thanks, Inoue.
What? Karin chose Inoue's dad.
It's just random, I'm sure of it.
Really? Do you have a good reason? Yes.
Why? What?
See?
What? Nothing's coming out.
Nothing's coming out... the face.
No way. It looks like Inoue-san.
His face looks like Mr. Inoue. But that's what I meant. His face looks like Mr. Inoue.
He's got a good-looking face.
He must be good-looking. He is good-looking.
Oh, yes, thank you.
Why did you choose Karin?
I don't know, Karin...
She doesn't say much.
I totally get it.
I get it. You're so determined.
She seems poised.
What about you, Kira? And Karin?
Yes.
She seems like she's quietly looking around.
She doesn't say much, but she seems to be watching over you.
By the way, Tamura-san, what exactly did you put in this?
It's amazing.
The colors are amazing.
Anko (red bean paste), chocolate and mochi (rice cake).
It's like a sweet.
Looks delicious.
I'm so happy for you guys!
Like this.
It's so good!
Arrangement
I have no idea about takoyaki!
Next mom
So many ideas!
Mom, I'll think of new ways to make takoyaki.
I want to try Kimcheese.
Kimcheese is good, yes, let's make it!
I want to eat Kimcheese, Karin!
Who's your mom?
Daddy's not moving at all.
He says it's good if everyone stands firm.
That's not true.
Dad is the one who cooks for the family.
Dad, I'll move.
Hang in there, Dad.
Will you, Mom?
Mom, I'm sure she will.
I think we'd be a match.
Honestly, I want it all to be your mom.
She's so solid.
That's what I'm saying.
But, you know, for the six of us.
Do you have any pets?
I liked the pets.
What do you mean, you liked them?What do you mean?
I've made up my mind.
I'm going in.
Ready?
Okay...
It's Takemoto san...
You know...
There's a surprisingly good point
The most flowers
The most
Takoyaki-san
Second best
Why?
I'm Takemoto san
Everyone's so disparate
You're definitely not Takemoto san
Why?
You're so determined
That's why
You'll do the schoolwork.
I'm sure you'll do it
I'm gonna be able to come to school.
Today's good.
I helped her with her homework.
I helped him with his homework.
You're a mom.
What's with the fire?
Dad said you picked it out.
He said you picked it out.
No, I didn't.
I'm sorry, Meesan.
No, I'm not.
If it doesn't apply to your father and mother...
I was thinking Flame.
But in this case, the flame should be the father.
And the mother is Mi-san.
It's going to work out, isn't it?
I'll miss you.
Mi-san...
Mi-chan will be spoiled by the flame just right.
We're going to be a great family.
I thought
I'm sure you'll take that pampering in stride.
and says it herself.
You're so good at spoiling him.
I think it'd be so cute to have a mom like her.
Really?
Yes!
I'm going to be a cute mom.
What else is in the family?
Big brother or big sister?
That's a good idea.
I'm going for big sister.
Big sister. Big sister. Big sister.
They can't be in the same room.
That's the way it's going to be.
Sis, sis, sis, pet.
Grandma
Grandpa.
No, they're not.
Two rows.
What's left?
A sister and a brother.
Or sisters.
We'll put them together.
One slot for your sister, your sister.
And one sister-brother slot.
Pet.
Then...
You choose one person in the "big sister, big sister" slot.
You have to choose one person from the "big sister" group.
It can't be the same person, right?
Who's your choice now?
Who'll be the mom?
The dog plant...
Who chose the flame?
Sis.
There were two
Two.
Which one of you wants to be a mom?Which one of us wants to be a mom?
I'll decide after that one.
I'm serious.
There's only one question left.
I can't read it.
Turn it over.
Oh!
It's so beautiful.
It smells so good.
Anko anko anko anko
So good
So beautiful.
That's the most beautiful thing I've seen today.
It's so good!
This is great!
What's going on here?
What did you put in it?
Kimcheese, as requested by Takemoto san
Here, cod roe...
Seven chocolates...
Calico!
What should I do with the empty ones?
I want to put something in it.
Quail?
I'll put a quail.
It won't explode.
The egg fell out.
I'll put a quail in.
Blah, blah, blah.
What if it explodes?
It smells so good.
When it's Mr. Bamboo...
Smell it.
I don't know.
It's like a dreamland.
It smells like a dreamland.
Smells like dreamland.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
Like churros.
Excuse me.
I'm not coming in.
I'm trying.
I don't know how to get it.
It's so frustrating to go through Japan's best.
What are you going to do?
What about questions?
I'll go next time.
Next time!
You know, I'm looking for questions.
We've only got one question.
You and Mom haven't decided yet.
I've already decided on a mom.
Mom, Dad, and the kids.
Sorry, guys.
It's just that we've decided that you're Kali.
So...
Let me go next.
I'll go next.
Let's see...
I'm going to ask you a question.
It's a picture of the two Tsumuzi.
Question, question, question, question.
I'm going to ask you a question
Bamboo skewer
I'm sorry, one of the turners is missing.
I'm working on it.
It's coming from a great place.
I don't know how to do this anymore.
Here they come.
Look at this.
I'll just do one.
I'll do it again.
Do it again.Let's do it again.
Look.
Can I ask you one favor?
Yes, ma'am.
At least this time of night, don't make it sound like I'm talking to you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't help it.
I've been trying from the beginning.
Please, please, please.
This one.
Don't talk back to Mee-chan.
I don't think so.
She's going to be in the picture, right?
Let's vorrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!
That's the one that's going to get you.
I've been voracious.
Everyone's been here for an hour.
No one's cutting me off.
Hey, guys...
I heard about Kira-chan...
Inoe-san's story.
What she's complaining about...
I put in a vortex, but it's not that interesting.
But if you look at it from the side...
It sticks out.
It's a vortex.
Let's see what happens now.
Yay!
That's what he wanted to say.
I see... did you guys hear Mi-chan's request?
Yes, they did.
She wants you to use honorifics, right?
What, the other way around?
Is that a good idea?
Shall we cut it off?
Let's cut the top off, too.
How did you cut it for six?
I cut them in half and then I cut three lengthwise.
Cut a line in half.
Three.
Then one or two.
Thanks to you, Mi-chan.
I can't get the chocolate to melt.
Teach me how to do it.
I'll do my best.
You're going to stick it in?
Shall we all follow you?
It looks so good!
I'm so happy.
I have a question for you, Kira-chan.
If you had one more slot for Kira Kids...
Who among today's members
Who do you think would be a good member?
Fujiha, right?
Ms. Fujiha.
Wait a minute.
I like you.
You seem to like her.
You can't get someone you can't have
I can make a reason for them to be mine
I can use that as a reason to own her.
To get Ms. Fujiha.
To get her.
I want to be in the Kira Kids
but I can't throw away Mr. Takemoto
I can't throw them away
Can't put it down, why?
Because they're cute
Kira, you're the cutest
I like that you don't come to the top
You're right.
You know what?
They updated the blog.
You and Kira were battling earlier.
Kira and I were fighting earlier.
I wanted to update the blog by 10:00 a.m.
Takemoto-san was struggling, too.
The moment I finished sending it off...
The moment it was updated...The moment it was updated
I love it.
It was so fake!
What? You don't want it?
Don't want it?
It's totally fine, but I think it's great and delicious.
I'd like to try takoyaki kuru for the first time.
What's wrong with it? I'm sure you'll want it, it looks so good...
Thank you very much!
Nakata I can't either, thank you, sorry. Wow, you did your job, thank you, thank you!
I'm so glad you're okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay...
Until the takoyaki is done...
I'll comment until the takoyaki is done.
First of all, I'd like to recommend the most famous place in Kansai to all the fans of takoyaki.
Thank you... if you have visitors from overseas, is there any food you would like to recommend?
Do you have any Kansai foods you'd like to recommend to foreign visitors?
If it's Hyogo... they have kashiyaki.
That's true, that's a good idea.
I've been told there's no such thing, but it's not a sauce, it's a soup and the dough is softer.
It's made with fluffy eggs and soup stock.
They eat it in triplicate.
The "ataka-yaki" is amazing, quail's quail's quail's cheese's cheese, where is it?
Thank you very much!
akashi is a very tasty place... akashi is also made of akashi.
Not just for dipping in white sushi... no, no, no!
I used to want to try it, but it's definitely something with egg and sourdough, right?
I'd like to try it.
I'd eat it.
Cigars are a rare food. I recommend it to everyone.
I'd like to recommend it to everyone overseas...and if Mr. Tamura makes it for us, we'll have a little bit of it.
ம10 talk hot cake
I'll do it after feeding gaga closed a
I'm so glad you guys tried it!
I heard it's a sensation echo!
I've never made this before, but it's my first time and I'm ready for anything!
I'm so excited because I can't wait for my week to get going!
I'm looking forward to it!
I can't wait to try it!
Amazons are good, baico heat sound!
It's more or less cold, right?
That sight
That's what I'm talking about!
I thought Kansai was supposed to be slow and tender.
It's okay.
Someone helped!
I got you out.
Do you want some electricity?
Can I take it? Here.
Mmm, it's delicious. Do you want to try another one? This was delicious.
I'll make another one? Do you guys want some? I want some!
Let's make it. - What a pleasure!
Can we make a "What's the point?" flavor?
Is that okay? Is it ready? Should we turn it off?
Wait a minute... Quail... who wants quail?
It's got so much chocolate in it.
It's good, right? Is it good?
It's already done.
It's okay, it's okay.
Why did you switch them?
It's perfect.
Let's go, Akarin!
Takemoto-san, I finished the kimchee you wanted.
Thank you
Make me another one.
Please do
So popular.
What's that? That one?
Thank you.
Okay, I'll explain it to you as I make it so you can make it.
Okay, I'll go through first. Can I go this way first?
Let's start with this.
Looks like an assistant.
It's far away, but it's okay.
What's this? Looks like an assistant.
There are only assistants.
Look at that picture.
Where's the camera?
This is it. Thank you very much.
Please, sir.
Let's begin.Begin.
Okonomiyaki seeds.
Is it done?
Just one ladle, sir.
It's a cooking show.
If it's a cooking show...
Just one ladle.
Thank you very much.
May I have some cabbage?
You had cabbage.
You did.
How much do you want?
I'd like to reflect Inoue's opinion.
Thank you.
I need a mentality.
Do you have a mentality?
One?
I'll go a little further.
Three?
I'll give you a few more.
I'll go a little further. Five. Cabbage peeking out?
Five times on the bridge. I don't get many on the bridge.
Cabbage, camera, this one. What shall we do now?
Okay? Thank you very much.
May I have some red bean paste? How much should I put in?
Two-thirds of this. Two-thirds.
Can I see it? I'll start from the top. I'm sorry.
Anko... anko... anko... anko...
To get the bean jam? Anko, two thirds of this.
I want it. It's good. Yes, it's surprisingly good.
A little more, but shall I put it in first? But it's okay.
Just a little more. I'll put it in later.
I'll take Kira's stain.
Thank you, Kira!
Okay, I dropped this. Just a little more.
Next?
Kira!
Thank you very much. What's next, teacher?
Here's your chocolate.
I'm sorry, I stepped on it.
I'll leave it to you. It's not every day I get to see Tamura-san's hair.
Stop it, Doraemon.
Do you want me to put it in? Put it in?
Doggie, Doggie, Doggie, that's chocolate and kimchi.
It's nice that you guys are asking questions at all.
Wow!
4 re wh
креп flight
I'm sorry, I'm just trying to get this thing going.
I'm sorry, I was just trying to make the election.
I've seen something like this before, to a cat
Hey, have you seen this before? Look, everyone, look, four people, a thousand people.
A thousand thousand thousand, it sure looks like four people
It looks like four people, right?
This was an accident, actually I'd say there were two, but wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
I'll be right back...
I'd like to serve it with the 4 of us.
Sorry, excuse me.
What did you do?
If you do it...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
4... please eat the takoyaki...
Can I come in while you read the comments?
I should've warmed it up for you.
I'll be getting more soon! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
ohohohohohohohohohohohohoh..............
wow!
a I'm making more than just wow, wow, wow... English
añés pao 對不對
I'm sorry, but I'm botenz.
Sorry, this one doesn't cost anything. I'm sorry.
What is it now?
Oh, oh, among us.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Congratulations
I'm so happy for you. I'm going to bake.
Thank you.Thank you.
That's great that you're doing this live.
That's great.
I'm so happy.
Kira's so happy.
Yay!
Thank you, Kira!
Thank you so much.
So cute!
Let's eat takoyaki.
Look at my quail.
Look at my takoyaki.
My quail takoyaki turned out like this.
That's not good.
It's just an apology.
This apology!
Oh, really!
Celebrating our 100,000th customer!
Wow.
Octopus Sweets.
This is really good!
I want to do this!
Please do it!
I'll send you the recipe!
Congratulations!
Takoyaki (octopus dumplings)
Congratulations on the bean paste!
This is kimchi!
Choco wask's eyes.
Yes, I understand
This is chocolate.
I thought it was kimchi and ate it as if it was kimcheeze, but it turned out to be a little too much, so I went back to thinking it was fine. I thought it was fine, but chocolate is a real sweet!
It's really delicious and tasty!
Chocolate is so good!
It's good! Let's eat!
Let's eat! You made chocolate? It's so good! What did Karin make?
She put some mental pills in it. You want some mental pills?
Karin, who's this week's kimchi? Spicy and delicious!
Sunflower made it. I put kimchi and Fujii put cheese.
To the stars! Know how I feel!
I'm going to the stars!
We'll eat quail, quail, quail, quail, quail.
I'll eat it, I'll eat it, I'll eat it, I'll eat it, I'll eat it, I'll eat it, I'll eat it...
It's delicious this way!
It separated the moment I put it in my mouth. Zero.
How's the takoyaki texture? Takoyaki on the left cheek, zero on the right.
But of course it's delicious.
Good, good, good.
How cute is that dress... all of a sudden?
Let's have a look.
Oh, my God.
It's so cute.
Takoyaki's the best!
Pero's looks good, too.
If I fail, I'll probably fall a little short of getting to 200,000 next time.
I'd like to say 1,000,000, but I'm not sure what's in it.
I got rice cake, chocolate, red bean paste and cabbage...
The second part... What should I do with it?
It's delicious, isn't it? Wait, this is a little dangerous.
It was so good even after a long time. I'll make it again.
Tantai-ko is delicious.
Aim for 200,000! Aim for 200,000!
Go for it.
Can you make it? Ready!
Oh!
It's gone!
It's so good! It smells so good! Does it smell this good the moment they move in?
Does it smell good? I knew it smelled like dreamland the moment they moved in.
That's my mom! It's Mom! - Phenomenon.
It's delicious.
Thank you. And I put a little too much rice cake in it.
But it's good with rice cakes. It's delicious, isn't it?
There were noodles on the table, but Hiroshima-yaki means Hiroshima noodles stuck on okonomiyaki.
Inoue said he wanted yakisoba.
I see!
So that's how it is!
So we don't have to make it?
Can we eat it? Can we eat it?
Do you want to make yakisoba?
Yakisoba.
I'll do it.I'll do it.
Yakisoba noodles with bean sprouts, right?
Do you cut it? I have scissors and a knife.
No problem. It's fine when making yakisoba.
Cut it into bite-size pieces?
Cut?
Stir-fry this and the meat.
Do you want some tomatoes? I can't.
Do you put meat in yakisoba?
You want to cook, Kei?
What do you want? What do you want to bring?
I don't know if I want to make yakisoba.
Oh, wait, there's some leaves.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
That was close.
You got burned.
My 100,000th anniversary.
I'd like you to try this one.
I'd like you to eat it.
Then I'll just sit here.
Let's eat.
I think I'll have this first.
That looks delicious.
When this is done, we can have it.
Yeah. Yakisoba.
No.
Yakisoba.
I was going to say yakisoba.
I don't like yakisoba.
It's going well.
Like 1,000 people.
Oh, my God!
One hundred and three thousand and three.
I think we've got about 15 minutes.
Oh, I'm so sad.
How many tens of thousands do you think we can get?
I don't know.
I'd like to make 100,000.
I'd like to get to 100,000 by the time we do this thing.
Yeah, where do you guys want to set your sights?
Right now.
1400 for 100,000.
Okay, I see.
Ten minutes!
Oh, my God!
How's that? That's it.
Can we get 10,000?
100,000!
Can we get 110,000?
I wanna go!
Oh, it smells so good... that aroma has given me the urge to eat again, so I'm sure I can make it.
I'm sure you'll be able to make it.
I'm suddenly confident.
But you're getting better and better... and it's only 10 minutes to 11:30!
He doesn't want to eat rolled noodles.
Thank you.
Go get some for me, please.
Thank you for the food on the side, and for the questions.
Thank you.
I'm glad you asked.
Hmm?
Snacks for everyone.
Oh, I'm gonna eat this.
Thank you.
Thank you very much. Ahhh! Sorry, someone.
All right.
Thank you very much.
All right
Do you cook at home or don't you cook at home?
Thank you, you're cute
Thank you, I'll cook then? Thank you very much. Here you go, Mr. Exber.
Thank you very much.
You're going to cook with Inoue-san, too. You don't want it yet? You don't want it yet?
Just one? If it sounds bad...
Which camera? But it might work.
What's this? This?
They're gonna eat the real thing.Everybody eats real food!
I don't have any!
The meat is about to burn. Let's go.
Wait, what's going on?
Let's grill the board.
Oh, oh, my hand!
I lost my mark.
I'm sorry.
Which way shall we go?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
Just as well.
I've got so much meat on my hands.
It's like a real home party,
I love the way the cushions are scattered.
It's true.
It sure looks like everyone's kicking it.
It's really nice.
It's like a real home party,
When you do it like this, it's like a mess.
Do you want to put that much in?
You can put as much as you want.
Let's eat it grilled.
It's yakisoba.
What is this?
Mochi.
The meat is cooked a little too well. It was lettuce. It was cabbage.
I put it in the rice cake with the toy and ate it. I couldn't get it off.
Yes, once.
A little meat.
Oh, yum.
This looks good. You must be starving. This is a great video.
Listen to the sound. The sound.
That sound is good, isn't it? I know, right?
I love the sound.
Wow, that's a nice video. That's a nice video.
The meat was still red.
I had to cut it while it was cooking.
It's a bit... piggy. Let's cook it well.
Hey, Bahan...
It's sizzling!
I lost my iPad.
Here it is.
Are there any questions?
I'll look for it.
Uh-huh.
But there's more.
Really?
Ask me a question.
Shall I put it in?
It's a little crispy.
I think I can make it.
Can we get 110,000?
I don't know.
Everyone says it's rice.
I'm sure they are.
Here it comes! Noodles!
That's right.
Nice video.
Salt and pepper.
What's that with all the members here?
If you could say where you want to go, where would you go?
But what would you like to do if you could go to a different place than Kansai?
I'm curious about that.
How much sleep do you guys get on average?
Average is average.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for the 102,000... a little bit of idleness.
I think it's the juice. How many hours?
I'm just looking for something.
It depends on how many hours Koike-san works on average.
I've been doing it for an average of 7 hours.
I understand... but it's like you're trying to get to sleep in 17 hours.
Thank you.
Oh, that's a lot.
We're almost done, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, my God!
It's a little hard to mix.
You guys are pretty good for people who say they don't cook.They're good for a guy who said he doesn't cook.
They were a little worried at first.
You cook.
You do?
Hey. - Hey.
Hey.
What do you cook?
Maybe not... not really
But every time I look at a recipe, I'm sure I'll know what to look for.
Inawawa is pretty good, no matter what you look at
I don't know if I'm quick
I don't know how quick I am
I used to make my own rice at the Showa Kons and I wanted to have omelettes for a snack.
I made omelettes every day for snacks
I ate more rice than sweets... which means I was making it right.
I mean, you know, when we have pot luck parties, we can make zosui (rice porridge) or whatever it's called, with real recipes.
I can do it... and there's this thing about gastronomy...
That's what's great, isn't it? Gastronomy?
Gastronomy... Gastronomy...
Gourmet... Gourmet...
Cute. A gourmet.
By the way, do you have any tips on how to make Inoue's yakisoba?
You put water in it and steam it, so it's more...
It's softer and more tender.
But with salt and pepper, it's delicious.
But it's still good enough.
Because the sauce is delicious.
Because the sauce is good, people will eat it.
I want to eat it, I want to eat it, I want to eat it, I want to eat it, I want to eat it so bad!
It's good. It's good.
It's good. Please give me a plate.
But maybe it's my imagination... or the chocolate... or the fact that the sauce is so thick... but... udon noodles, for example...
But udon noodles... aren't they thicker in the Kanto region?
Thank you.
I'd love to answer your most important question.
I'd like to answer your questions.
I'm sending you something... like indoor-outdoor, and then indoor.
Indoor-outdoor, indoor-outdoor, depends on the day... but I'm definitely an indoor person.
I'm definitely an indoor person. I can get outdoors if I can turn it on.
I also walk a lot. My goal is 30,000 steps and I walk a lot.
I go to the park to play. I usually go to the park.
Okay, Mr. Mee, go ahead. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your questions. Do you have a good lecture you'd like to give?
Yes! I want to eat!
Yes! I want you to do the game! I want to!
Tamura-san, Ten-san, do you play games? Yeah, they do.
The other day, Ten-chan said she was good at Splatoon.
She was playing the game while yelling at the top of her lungs at the conference.
He was playing it.
He said he was with Mr. Tanaka from Angie's Angie's.
He said he got beat up by Ten and bullied by him.
He said he was bullied by the heavens?
He said that the highest rank was... when he came to see me at Sakurabee.
Thank you. Thank you. Is this Kira's?
Can I have some of your okonomiyaki?
He asked for time for a photo op. - That's right.
Where? Where? This one here... This one... will it capture all of us?
I'm sorry, my timing is perfect. It's my fault.
Thank you so much! It's going to work!
Are you sure it'll work? Are you in? Sorry, Karin. Thank you.
Is everyone in? Do you think it'll look good? Yes, it looks like home. It's so nice. Perchie.
Who's there? I'm sorry, my face looks terrible.
Oh, wait a minute, what do you want me to do? What do you want me to do?
Oh, it looks great. It's on the camera guy's head.
Cheese!
I'll be right out, so let's have some of L'Ollorger's Tiree and Fried Noodles.
Oh, you stupid german line.
Hey!
Oil is the way to go
El nah
I'll get it over here, over here, over here, over here.
That's not what I want.
It's okay. - Boobie, um...
Where's the camera, where's the camera, where's the camera, where's the camera?
I know you're mad about everything, but yes, it happens.
But yes, this happens sometimes... and he doesn't do anything.
I'm impressed... not even a little bit...
There's not even a little bit more krp oil!
orsher! Yakiso yasobo!
yui, you can try to make it prettier.
I can make it prettier!Cute.
Yui's cute. Just because I'm cute doesn't mean I'm not cute.
It's really not at all. You two are so adorable.
They're so cute!
Well, well, well.
I made it sound like there's something going on. Sorry, stop it.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no. Koike is doing a Cinderella play.
You're so good! I can admire you so much!
I'm sorry, everyone.
Was it cold?
Was it cold? Was it cold?
Yakisoba noodles are in the freezer.
Yakisoba is ready. Let's eat.
It's perfectly normal.
It's all right, isn't it? - What?
Bon appétit. - Bon appétit what?
What happened? What happened?
Everyone just ate and ate, just eating yakisoba.
Noodles with bean sprouts. All bean sprouts.
I always think it's noodles, but it's only bean sprouts.
That's Inome's way of sorting things out.
All bean sprouts. No kidding, all bean sprouts.
No, it's not that, Kira. It's delicious.
How is it without bean sprouts? No, it's not.
It's grilled bean sprouts. Delicious!
That's right. Let's eat.
Did you put the noodles in? Yes, I did.
Yes, they're in. Are you guys sure they're in?
Yes, they're in, because, look, look, look.
Look, it's only bean sprouts.
I'm pretty well stuffed, but Inome can't really divide it into six equal portions.
It's very loving. I'm dividing it by feelings.
It's not about the number of people... it's about the feeling.
I'm sharing with Gumshi and Momochan, too.
It's not the number of people, it's the feeling.
It's getting bigger.
It's really good.
It's never going to stop.
It's going to go on forever, isn't it?
It's going on forever. Why? Why? Oh, my God, what's going on?
It's so good.
It's so good, it's cracking.
I wonder if there's an archive of these things?
I don't know.
It would be a little embarrassing.
Are you sure?
Yeah, well, it's just too sous-cheeky.
It was soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo.
No, not at all, but it was nothing out of the ordinary.
Yeah, nothing happened.
From the beginning to the end.
It was smooth, wasn't it?
There was nothing happening.
It was like, "Oh, it's raw.
Not at all.
Is it a recording? It was like...
It was a break from that.
It went too smoothly.
That's the funniest comment I've ever heard.
It's the most interesting comment.
And listen to this.
Jenga and a language called Cat's Ha.
I suggested it.
I thought it would be fun.
But make sure you do it right.
Let's say "har" this time.
Let's say "Hi" this time.
Are you sure?
Ha?
Can I say "har" now?
What?
Can I say "har"?
I want to say "har.
I know, I know.
You're very good at explaining it.
Let's see...
It's... it's...
It's delicious.
Yummy?Delicious?
One by one.
One is special.
After you choose a subject card.
I'll give you an act card.
Assign the situation
Assign
The player
perform the subject given to him or her
by voice and facial expression
Vote for the other players
Vote
Yes, sir.
Sorry, I thought it was game time.
of what I wanted to do.
This is what I really want to do
Just one at a time
Ha-ha-ha. - Ha-ha-ha. - Ha-ha-ha.
Can we play Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
And we'll guess.
Let's see what you got.
Ha-ha-ha.
I told Japan one more time to do it this way, this way, if you spill water again...
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I'll go back to the place where we played the game you wanted to play, and I'll make a plan for it.
I know, let's play a game together, if you want to go inside.
I had a lot of fun, and it was a lot of fun, even if it wasn't a live broadcast, because I could do it, and I did get to be a player.
Right?
I've been telling you that it seems like a lot of people are watching us.
People from all over Japan and even from overseas
I'm sure you can speak English, can't you?
I'm sure you'll meet Mr. Takemochi, who usually speaks in English, and go to the prefecture... and then there's the rest... Slow down!
I'm with you, I'm with you, I'm with you, I'm with you, I'm with you, I'm with you, I'm with you.
I'm so glad to see you!
Oh miss 4 miss 4 m Sue I love you so much!
All by myself from now on and from now on please continue to support me in the back g 6 of the treasure house
I'm sorry, I can't do it for the show, but I remember it, and I've only got one in-between.
Eggs once inside me... what was it?
I can't do it for the show!
I'm in love with you!
I want it, I want it, I want it.
I only want it now... because I want it.
I want you to... - Okay, in Chinese.
I'm sorry, can I sit here for a minute, it's a little bit cold, I don't know what it is, but it's a little bit cold, and it's like that again, and it's like a carpet, a carpet that's cool, and it's like that again, and it's like that again.
I'll let you do that.
Okay, Ami-chan, what is it?
What's that?
Oh, okay.
4C!
Wait a minute. That was terrible.
That was terrible.
Can we just do the in-between?
4C, right?
Invan 46.
Yes, sir.
Okay, Ami-chan.
Ready!
4C!
I changed it to 4C.
I think they're watching.
Even people from overseas.
Shay shay weee-oh.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I want to learn English with you all, and I'm looking forward to practicing English conversation a little bit.
I think there are people who want to learn English conversation.
I think there are people who want to learn English conversation. Let's do it.
Let's do it.
I want to do this thing.
I want to play games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games, games
I want to play in that game, too, you know, without the realistic puzzle-solving.
I'd like to go to the festival and have Scrap make one for me, and I'd like to be locked up in a room and solve riddles together.
I'd like to do more of that... and there's a lot of things I'd like to do.
But whose valley do you want to go to?
I wonder...
A live-action version of Onuma Akiho-chan's swamp song.
She made a music video for it... and bought a real costume she'd worn before.
So she's making it real... so we'll be able to see it...
I've seen it! I've seen it!
It started with a swamp song, Sakurazaka Channel, wasn't it amazing?
Isogawa, Isogawa... wasn't it great?I had the Iso River, the Kappa River, the Isogawa River, the Isogawa River...
We'll be back next week.
We had an okonomiyaki party today.
I hope we can communicate with you again in the future.
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button!
I've always wanted to say this. Let's all say it together!
That's all for this okonomiyaki party. Thank you very much!